Temiloluwa S. Abebiyi

Personal details

Temiloluwa S. Abebiyi

diamondtemmy456@gmail.c

inl

Temiloluwa (Diamond)Adebiyi



Success temmy



Discord: Defibeast#0723

Skills

Great analytics and research methodology

Computer literacy

Technical and Fundamental analyst

Managerial and marketing expertise

Defi Trader and Tutor

Hobbies

- Movie
- Games
- Networking with new friends

INTEREST

Finance and Technology

Blockchain education

Accounting

Computer literacy

Profile

Seasoned, innovative and equally insightful fundamental analyst with extensive knowledge in Blockchain tech. With 24months experience and a track record of achievements in developing and implementing professional market research and trade strategies with extra ordinary results.

With added knowledge in technical analysis, Research methodology, Decentralized Finance tutelage, Project management and marketing. I have a significant ability to work and perform in term environments and also on my own initiative.

Educational History

2019 - Present

Bsc Accounting University of Lagos

Nirvana Academy

2021

Certification in DeFi analytics, trade and research

WORK EXPERIENCE

Ophir Institute

2021 - Present

- Works in the marketing and PR department
- Advisory to the expansion of Blockchain consultancy and Edutech brand of the company

#WomenInDefi movement

2021 - Present

- Speaker and moderator
- Financial markets and Decentralized Finance Tutor
- Developed and implemented proper marketing strategies

NAVIKATZ NFT

2022 - Present

Community Moderator

CELODOGE

2022 - Present

Project researcher and manager

Crona Swap

2022 - Present

Community manager